[
    {
        "qid": 29980,
        "question": "Patient is a 12 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, right flank, upper chest, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 10 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and left scapula.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Boerhaave",
        "option2": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Pericarditis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "57%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 64131,
        "question": "Patient is a 8 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the right side of the chest, the left side of the chest, and the right posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option4": "Pneumonia",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 130287,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option4": "Panic attack",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 415813,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking, haunting, like a knife stroke, and violent.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, left flank, upper chest, right hypochondrium, and epigastric region.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine and the right scapula.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous and feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Boerhaave",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 819538,
        "question": "Patient is a 11 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heartbreaking, like a knife stroke, and violent.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, right flank, upper chest, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 8 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the thoracic spine, right scapula, and left scapula.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 9 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has vomited several times or has made several efforts to vomit.",
        "option1": "Boerhaave",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Pericarditis",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1113766,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is heavy.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head, forehead, right cheek, and right temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Acute otitis media",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option4": "Chagas",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 177632,
        "question": "Patient is a 59 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, sensitive, and sickening.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest, hypochondrium (left), and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Unstable angina",
        "option2": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 985534,
        "question": "Patient is a 57 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head, right cheek, left cheek, occiput, and right temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Cluster headache",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "95%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 529822,
        "question": "Patient is a 63 year old male.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Panic attack",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 749319,
        "question": "Patient is a 70 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, like a knife stroke, burning, and sickening.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, right hypochondrium, left hypochondrium, belly, and epigastric region.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has asthma or has had to use a bronchodilator in the past.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option2": "Pericarditis",
        "option3": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option4": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 922727,
        "question": "Patient is a 70 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, sensitive, and tugging.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left hypochondrium, belly, and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest and upper chest.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has asthma or has had to use a bronchodilator in the past.<br>- The patient thinks they are pregnant or are currently pregnant.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Stable angina",
        "option3": "Unstable angina",
        "option4": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 90600,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old male.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient has family members who have been diagnosed with anemia.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a cramp.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple and left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient has recently had stools that were black, like coal.<br>- The patient is taking new oral anticoagulants (NOACs).<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient has noticed light red blood or blood clots in their stool.<br>- The patient has traveled to Asia in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Cluster headache",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 78836,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the right side of the chest, and the left posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's vaccinations are up to date.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 81807,
        "question": "Patient is a 29 year old male.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "63%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 830733,
        "question": "Patient is a 57 year old male.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive, tugging, and exhausting.<br>- The patient feels pain at the back of the head, top of the head, and forehead.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient has recently had stools that were black (like coal).<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient has noticed light red blood or blood clots in their stool.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating that they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Cluster headache",
        "option2": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option3": "Anemia",
        "option4": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]